Donald E. Hattin Media Materials 1959/2016 PC006
Test - Paleontology Collection
- Reprint, 1959-2016
  - Chalk II (Box 8)
    - Miscellaneous Chalk papers (Box 8)
      - Depth estimates (Box 8, Folder 5)
      - Porosity (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - Chalk (Box 8, Folder 7)
      - Lists of Chalk refs. (Box 8, Folder 8)
      - New Chalk articles (Box 8, Folder 9)
      - New papers (Box 8, Folder 10)
      - Chalk refs – georef. (Box 8, Folder 11)
      - Foundering (Box 8, Folder 12)
      - Eocene Chalk (Box 8, Folder 13)
      - World Chalk Sem's (Box 8, Folder 14)
      - Letters Chalk, global (Box 8, Folder 15)
      - Chalk conference Denmark (Box 8, Folder 16)
      - Charlie Smith Chalk (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Chalk I (1894-1987) (Box 8, Folder 17)
      - Loose materials relating to Chalk (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Chalk II (1920-1995) (Box 8, Folder 17)
      - Loose materials relating to Chalk (Box 8, Folder 17)
      - Durham (Thesis) (Box 8, Folder 18)
      - G511 Scotian basin (Box 8, Folder 19)
      - G512 Corr. Of Scotian Basin w/ Georges Bank Basin (Box 8, Folder 20)
      - G512 U.K. Atlantic and Gulf Coastal Plain (Box 8, Folder 21)
      - Chalk Copenhagen (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Materials from unnamed box relating to Chalk (Box 8, Folder 22)
      - French journal article relating to Chalk (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Papers relating to the geology of Kansas (1868-2001) (Box 9)
    - Geology of Kansas (1868-1948) (Box 9)
    - Geology of Kansas (1949-1953) (Box 9)
    - Geology of Kansas (1955-1960) (Box 9)
    - Geology of Kansas (1968-2001) (Box 9)
  - Reprints of U.S. Paleontological and Geological journals and articles (Box 10)
    - Journal articles and bulletins (Box 10)
    - Richards 1958 N.J. (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - International reprints I (Box 11)
    - Cretaceous V (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Cretaceous Y (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Cretaceous Z (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Zullo (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Arabia Abu Dhabi ETO (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Africa- General (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Albania (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Australia (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Belgium (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Cyprus (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Denmark (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Egypt (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Europe: General (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Paleogeography Europe (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Florida Straits (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - France (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - General Mortimore (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - GDR (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Germany (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Greece (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Guyots (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Hatton Rochall Trough (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Hungary (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Iraq (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Ireland (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Israel (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Jordan (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Lebanon (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - International reprints II (Box 12)
    - Bioturbation/ Tiering (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Canada Inoceramus (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Placonopsis (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Whiteaves (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Troger (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Toshimoto (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Tanabe (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Drushchits (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Marcinowski (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Surlyk (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - And loose reprints (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Foreign language reprints (Box 13)
    - Loose articles in Russian, French, German, etc (Box 13)
    - Jurassic – Saskatchewan and Manitoba (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - U.S. and international reprints (contains maps) (Box 14)
    - Loose journal articles and maps (Box 14)
  - Book reprints and miscellaneous materials (Box 15)
    - Personal Collection of Books (Box 15)
      - Illinois Geological Survey (Box 15)
      - Sea-Level Changes: An integrated Approach (Box 15)
      - Symposium on Cyclic Sedimentation (Box 15)
      - Bibliography of Kansas Geology 1823-1984 (Box 15)
      - Selected speeches (Box 15)
      - State of Florida Department of Conservation (Box 15)
      - Geological Survey of Canada (Box 15)
      - Carbonate Rock Constituents Textures cements and porosities (Box 15)
    - Miscellaneous Materials (Box 15)
      - Granular Se. Rocks calcification (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - Percent Diagrams (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - Visual Estimation chart (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - Menzel (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - Coccoliths (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - Radiolaria (Box 15, Folder 6)
      - Synchronous Beds (Box 15, Folder 7)
      - Rate of DED (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - Facies Transitions (Box 15, Folder 9)
      - Structure: Penecontemporary (Box 15, Folder 10)
      - Ramp (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - Poem (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous reprints with annotations and manuscript materials I (Box 16)
    - Black Shale MS. (Hand drawn charts) (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Inoceramus Differentiation (chart) (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - KE Annona (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Insoluble Residue Study Niobrara (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Black Beauty Coal Co. (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Black Beauty Coal Co. (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Cirriped Bibliography (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Univ. of Colorado Cirriped Specimens (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Balthatser Fossil Localities (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Comparison of British and US West. INT Chalks (Chart) (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Zoological Record on CD ROM (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Lack of Hardgrounds (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Neogoniolithon Long Version with All Petrographs (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Bridge Creek Bulletin (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - W. Interior X Section (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Manfred Storr (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Burrowed Burrows (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Photomic Instructions Dodd (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - PaleoKarst (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Serpula (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - NSF New Section Niobrara (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Lucina (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Juvenile Rudists KN (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Bibliography on Shell bed Taphonomy (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Taphonomy References (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Laminations (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Greenhorn Insolubles (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Insoluble Residue Analysis of the Upper Cretaceous Greenhorn Limestone (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Chemical Analysis Bridge Creek (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - KGH-CHEM (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Newfoundland (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Substrate Paper notes (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Exploring Ancient Seas (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Niobrara Epizoans (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Revision of Nomencal. KGH (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Greenhorn Gas Well Log (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - Cirripeds Map and Tables (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Bullopora (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - NSF Trophic Analysis (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Niobrara "notes" (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - Cirriped Catalog Numbers (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - Decapods (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - Cret. Bryozoa (Box 16, Folder 43)
    - Cretaceous Global Cycles (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - Cretaceous Paleontology (Box 16, Folder 45)
    - Ammonite Generic characteristics (Box 16, Folder 46)
    - King Interpretation (Box 16, Folder 47)
    - Greenhorn Diagenesis Notes Drawing (Box 16, Folder 48)
    - Revision paper H and K (Box 16, Folder 49)
    - Milankovitch Symp. (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - Miscellaneous reprints with annotations and manuscript materials II (Box 17)
    - Plume Impingement Model (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Exploring Ancient Seas (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Lilly Conference (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - KY Coal (Cobb) (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Techniques (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Manuscript proofing symbols (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Instructor Evaluation Form (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Termites (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous Reprints (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous reprints with annotations and manuscript materials III (Box 18)
    - Ann. Activities 1995 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Vita (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Early Lithification for McCormick's Paper (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Hirt-Zeugmatolepas Computer Disc (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Submarine Fan (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Guyot (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Gas (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Oil Production (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Reservoir Character (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Seismic (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Unconformity (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Hardgrounds (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Cementation: Hardground (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Fecal Pellets (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Phosphate (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Glauconite (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Strat (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - External Events Solution Brecciation (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Minerals (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Texture Written (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Diag./ Mineralogy (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Geochem. (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Fractures – written rough draft (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Bentonite (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Thickness (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Dip (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Porosity (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Chemical Analysis (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Insoluble Residues (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Framework (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Porosity – written (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Faults – written done (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Bedding (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Structure Fractures (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Water Movement (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Clay Minerals in Kanas Cretaceous (Abstract) (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Greenhorn, Rough Draft (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Cimarron County Section (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Carlile Fossil Localites (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Indiana Stratigraphy (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Permian Nanno Fossils, Kansas (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Composite Type Keld and Assiniboline members, Vermillion River, Manitoba (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - Cimarron Copy (with charts) (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Bushinsky (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - Miscellaneous reprints with annotations and manuscript materials IV (Box 19)
    - Preservation Rough Drafts (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Preservation Refs. (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - #0000 IUGS Time Chart (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - 1989-1990 NACSN Post Nov 1989 Meeting (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - British Cret Chart (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Lithologic Units (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - KGH Measurements (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Tesnus Depositional Tectonic Setting (Figure) (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Probability Paper (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Cretaceous A (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Bottjer (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Skeletal Mineralogy Reprints (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Bergquist (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Greenhorn, N. Mex. (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Greenhorn- Dep. and Environ. Factors (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Masse and Philip 1972 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Yezoites (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Canright (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - History of Geology (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Gobetz (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Dodd (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Hattin – Vita (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Hirschmann (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Manning, Earl (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Mound (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Campbell (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Penny Padgett (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Rhoades (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Suttner (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Shaver (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - 1953-1954 Department Photo Raymond (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Lane (Box 19, Folder 32)
- Maps, 1959-2016
  - Maps I (Box 20)
  - Maps II (Box 21)
  - Maps III (Box 22)
    - General maps (Box 22)
    - Topographic maps (Box 22)
    - Stratigraphic maps (Box 22)
    - Field maps (Box 22)
    - Physiographic diagrams/types (Box 22)
    - Stratigraphic documentation (Box 22)
  - Maps IV (Box 23)
- Personal Collection, 1959-2016
  - Personal collection of negatives I (Box 24)
    - Includes box of Kodachrome slides (Box 24, Small-box 1)
  - Personal collection of negatives II (Box 24)